(Girl:)The puzzles were...
were really fun.
(Girl:)I've never had
to translate Klingon
(Girl:)into ancient Sanskrit before.
(Leonard:)Well...
careful, hmm, it's addictive.
Chija''e'vlKub je.
(Vanessa:)Or, as they say
in Sanskrit...
(Vanessa:)Ahm asman matey-bee
ta-teyva.
(Sheldon:)And just like that, you're
a Klingon-Sanskrit junkie.
Anyway, I-I just... I knew
I had to meet the person
(Vanessa:)responsible for such
a brilliant idea.
(Vanessa:)And I don't need to tell you,
there aren't a lot of men
(Vanessa:)who love physics, archaic languages
and flags of the world.
(Sheldon:)I am a bit of a unicorn.
(Sheldon:)Well, you certainly seem
(Sheldon:)like a special lady,
uh, but as you know,
(Sheldon:)you missed the deadline,
so thanks for playing.
(Raj:)How could you
send her away?!